<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30DaysApp</string>
    <string name="tittle">30 days of planes</string>

    <string name="plane_1_name">J-10 Vigorous Dragon</string>
    <string name="plane_2_name">Harrier GR9</string>
    <string name="plane_3_name">Dassault Rafale</string>
    <string name="plane_4_name">F-5 Freedom Fighter</string>
    <string name="plane_5_name">MiG-21 Fishbed</string>
    <string name="plane_6_name">F/A-18 Hornet</string>
    <string name="plane_7_name">Su-27 Flanker</string>
    <string name="plane_8_name">Messerschmitt Bf 109</string>
    <string name="plane_9_name">Shenyang J-11</string>
    <string name="plane_10_name">Saab JAS 39 Gripen</string>
    <string name="plane_11_name">F-35 Lightning II</string>
    <string name="plane_12_name">F-22 Raptor</string>
    <string name="plane_13_name">AV-8B Harrier II</string>
    <string name="plane_14_name">Eurofighter Typhoon</string>
    <string name="plane_15_name">MiG-29 Fulcrum</string>
    <string name="plane_16_name">Shenyang J-15</string>
    <string name="plane_17_name">Su-25 Frogfoot</string>
    <string name="plane_18_name">Su-35 Flanker-E</string>
    <string name="plane_19_name">Lockheed P-38 Lightning</string>
    <string name="plane_20_name">MiG-31 Foxhound</string>
    <string name="plane_21_name">Su-57 Felon</string>
    <string name="plane_22_name">Mirage 2000</string>
    <string name="plane_23_name">F-14 Tomcat</string>
    <string name="plane_24_name">Chengdu J-20</string>
    <string name="plane_25_name">AIDC F-CK-1 Ching-Kuo</string>
    <string name="plane_26_name">F-16 Fighting Falcon</string>
    <string name="plane_27_name">F-15 Eagle</string>
    <string name="plane_28_name">F-104 Starfighter</string>
    <string name="plane_29_name">F-4 Phantom II</string>
    <string name="plane_30_name">Hawker Hurricane</string>

    <string name="plane_1_description">The J-10 is a Chinese fourth-generation multirole fighter, designed by Chengdu Aircraft Corporation. It is used by the People\'s Liberation Army Air Force. It entered service in 2005. Its roles include air superiority and ground support.</string>
    <string name="plane_2_description">The Harrier GR9 is a British vertical take-off and landing (VTOL) fighter. It was used by the Royal Air Force and the Royal Navy. Introduced in 2006, it is an advanced version of earlier Harrier models. It was retired in 2010.</string>
    <string name="plane_3_description">The Rafale is a French multirole fighter of the 4.5 generation, produced by Dassault Aviation. It is capable of air combat, bombing, and reconnaissance missions. The Rafale entered service in 2001 and is mainly used by the French Armed Forces.</string>
    <string name="plane_4_description">The F-5 is a lightweight American fighter that entered service in the 1960s. Designed as a cost-effective aircraft, it was widely exported to various countries. The plane has been involved in numerous global conflicts. It is known for its simplicity and reliability.</string>
    <string name="plane_5_description">The MiG-21 is a Soviet fighter that entered service in the 1950s. It is one of the most mass-produced jet fighters in history. It has served in over 50 countries and participated in numerous conflicts.</string>
    <string name="plane_6_description">The F/A-18 Hornet is an American multirole fighter used by the U.S. Navy. It is capable of operating from aircraft carriers and performs both fighter and bombing missions. Introduced in 1983, it has participated in numerous conflicts.</string>
    <string name="plane_7_description">The Su-27 Flanker is a Soviet fourth-generation fighter, designed for air superiority. It is one of the most versatile and well-known combat aircraft in the world. It entered service in the 1980s and is still in use in many countries.</string>
    <string name="plane_8_description">The Messerschmitt Bf 109 is a German fighter used during World War II. It was one of the Luftwaffe\'s most important aircraft. During the war, it became one of the most successful fighters, with a high number of enemy aircraft shot down. It served in various versions until the end of the war.</string>
    <string name="plane_9_description">The Shenyang J-11 is a Chinese fighter based on the Soviet Su-27. It was produced under license and later developed in China. It is primarily used by the Chinese Air Force. The J-11 serves as an air superiority fighter.</string>
    <string name="plane_10_description">The Saab JAS 39 Gripen is a Swedish multirole fighter designed by Saab. It is one of the most advanced lightweight fighters. It was designed with multi-role capabilities and low operational costs in mind. The Gripen is used by several countries.</string>
    <string name="plane_11_description">The F-35 Lightning II is an American fifth-generation fighter capable of stealth operations. It comes in three variants, including carrier-based and vertical take-off models. The F-35 performs a wide range of tasks, including air combat, reconnaissance, and ground attacks.</string>
    <string name="plane_12_description">The F-22 Raptor is an American air superiority fifth-generation fighter. It has advanced stealth capabilities and is considered one of the best fighters in the world. Its primary mission is to gain air superiority over the enemy. It entered service in 2005.</string>
    <string name="plane_13_description">The AV-8B Harrier II is an American vertical take-off and landing fighter. Its ability to operate from short runways and ships is unique among combat aircraft. The Harrier II was widely used by the U.S. Marine Corps and participated in many conflicts around the world.</string>
    <string name="plane_14_description">The Eurofighter Typhoon is a multirole fighter designed by a consortium of European countries. It is used by several air forces, including the British, German, and Italian. The Typhoon is known for its advanced avionics and excellent maneuverability.</string>
    <string name="plane_15_description">The MiG-29 Fulcrum is a Soviet fourth-generation fighter designed for close-range combat and air superiority. It is known for its excellent maneuverability and powerful engines. The MiG-29 is used by many countries around the world.</string>
    <string name="plane_16_description">The Shenyang J-15 is a Chinese carrier-based fighter, based on the Soviet Su-33. It is used by the People\'s Liberation Army Navy on aircraft carriers. Its mission is to gain air superiority and support naval operations.</string>
    <string name="plane_17_description">The Su-25 Frogfoot is a Soviet ground attack aircraft designed to support ground operations. It is often compared to the American A-10 Thunderbolt II due to its purpose and durability. The Su-25 entered service in the 1980s and is still in use today.</string>
    <string name="plane_18_description">The Su-35 Flanker-E is a Russian multirole fourth-generation fighter. It is an evolution of the Su-27, with improved avionics, maneuverability, and modern weapon systems. The Su-35 is designed for air superiority and ground support operations.</string>
    <string name="plane_19_description">The Lockheed P-38 Lightning is an American fighter from World War II, characterized by its unique twin-boom design. It was used for intercepting enemy aircraft and reconnaissance missions. The P-38 played an important role in the Pacific theater.</string>
    <string name="plane_20_description">The MiG-31 Foxhound is a Soviet, and later Russian, long-range interceptor fighter. It was designed to intercept enemy aircraft and missiles in all weather conditions. The MiG-31 is one of the fastest fighters in the world, capable of reaching speeds over Mach 2.8.</string>
    <string name="plane_21_description">The Su-57 Felon is a Russian fifth-generation stealth fighter. It is designed for air combat, bombing, and reconnaissance. The Su-57 entered service in 2020 as Russia\'s answer to the American F-22 and F-35.</string>
    <string name="plane_22_description">The Mirage 2000 is a French multirole fighter designed by Dassault Aviation. It is used for both air combat and ground attacks. The Mirage 2000 has been widely exported and used in many armed conflicts worldwide.</string>
    <string name="plane_23_description">The F-14 Tomcat is an American carrier-based fighter used by the U.S. Navy. It gained widespread fame due to the movie "Top Gun." The F-14 was designed to intercept enemy aircraft at long distances. It served from the 1970s until 2006.</string>
    <string name="plane_24_description">The Chengdu J-20 is a Chinese fifth-generation stealth fighter. It was designed to achieve air superiority over its adversaries. The J-20 is the first Chinese combat aircraft of its kind to enter service in 2017.</string>
    <string name="plane_25_description">The AIDC F-CK-1 Ching-Kuo is a Taiwanese multirole fighter designed by the Aerospace Industrial Development Corporation. It is used by the Republic of China Air Force. The F-CK-1 entered service in the 1990s and is Taiwan\'s response to the threat posed by China.</string>
    <string name="plane_26_description">The F-16 Fighting Falcon is an American multirole fighter that entered service in the 1970s. It is one of the most versatile fighters in history, used by many countries. The F-16 is known for its excellent maneuverability and ground support capabilities.</string>
    <string name="plane_27_description">The F-15 Eagle is an American air superiority fighter that entered service in the 1970s. It was designed to dominate the skies and remains one of the most effective aircraft of its type. The F-15 has achieved an impressive number of air-to-air victories.</string>
    <string name="plane_28_description">The F-104 Starfighter is an American interceptor that entered service in the 1950s. It was one of the first aircraft capable of reaching speeds over Mach 2. Despite its innovative design, the F-104 gained a controversial reputation due to numerous accidents.</string>
    <string name="plane_29_description">The F-4 Phantom II is an American multirole fighter that entered service in the 1960s. It was widely used during the Vietnam War. The Phantom II was known for its speed and ability to carry a large amount of ordnance.</string>
    <string name="plane_30_description">The Hawker Hurricane is a British fighter from World War II that played a key role during the Battle of Britain. Although it was less advanced than the Spitfire, it shot down more enemy aircraft. The Hurricane was robust, easy to repair, and widely used by the RAF.</string>

    <string name="day_number">Day %d</string>
</resources>